

Larry Gonzales

larryg.dev@gmail.com | 210-279-5731 | larryg.tech | github.com/larryg727 | linkedin.com/in/larryg-dev

Summary

- * Full-stack developer with a strong passion for programming.
- * Transitioning from eight years in the appliance repair industry which utilized problem solving skills and adaptability.
- * Excited and eager to learn new things and push my abilities to overcome new challenges of solving complex problems as a member of a great development team.

Recent Projects

Fixithub - July 2017

A full-stack Java application that connects clients to appliance service companies. Users are able to search and schedule service appointments based on servicer submitted availabilities, view and submit reviews, and keep records of service.

Java | Spring Framework | MySQL JavaScript | Jquery | HTML | CSS Mobile Responsive

Texas Affordable Appliance - June 2017

A project to help a local appliance repair company build a web presence with a website. Site was created from the ground up including all content and images.

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Mobile

JQuery | Bootstrap | Goofle Maps API

Adlister - June 2017

A CMS web app that allows users to view, create, and browse ads created by users, as well as create an account theirselves. By integrating the MySQL database I was able to create, read, update, and delete user account and ad info to create this dynamic web app.

Java | MySQL | JSP | JSTL HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Mobile

Simple Simon - May 2017

A Simon memory game clone that is mobile responsive and implements features like a high-score, and standard and reverse levels. All logic and animations for this game are written in Javascript and JQuery.

JavaScript | Jquery

HTML | CSS | Mobile

Skills

Frontend

JavaScript | Jquery | HTML CSS | Bootstrap | ReactJs

Backend

Java | MySQL PHP | Spring Framework

Additional

JSON | AJAX | Git Flexbox | SASS | API's Mobile Responsive | MVC | CRUD

Personal

Fast Learner | Driven Self-starter | Knowledge-seeker

Experience

Allstar Appliance Repair, April 2016- March 2017 - Service Technician

- * Utilized problem solving and logic skills to properly diagnose and repair residential appliances.
- * Documented services and properly quote customers for services needed and rendered.
- * Maintained up to date knowledge of technical data and issues of specific industry

Appliance Parts Depot, October 2014- April 2016 - Customer Service Rep.

- * Guided customers though diagnosis and repair of appliances utilizing technical knowledge and problem solving skills.
- * Sold over \$60,000 monthly of appliance parts and accessories.
- * Maintained customer relations with service companies utilizing customer service skills.

Classic Appliance Repair, August 2013- October 2014 - Service Technician

- Utilized problem solving and logic skills to properly diagnose and repair residential appliances.
- * Documentedservices and properly quote customers for services needed and rendered.
- * Maintained up to date knowledge of technical data and issues of specific industry

Education

Codeup, March- July 2017

Completed an immersive fullstack developer program with over 536 hours of instruction and development of projects.

Capella University, 2015- 2016

Completed 24 credit hours towards the Information Technology degree program with a major in web development.